Previously on the show. Wolffy worked with the goats to catch his duplicates.
ความเดิมตอนที่แล้ว วูฟฟี่ร่วมมือกับพวกแกะจับตัวก๊อปปี้ของเขา
However, things kept going wrong at crucial moments.
เมื่อถึงช่วงเวลาสำคัญมักเกิดเหตุผิดพลาดเสมอ
After many defeats, the goats and the wolf
หลังจากแพ้มาหลายครั้ง แกะและหมาป่า
played cat and mouse with the duplicates and finally forced them to give in.
จึงเล่นเกมแมวจับหนูกับพวกตัวก๊อปปี้ ในที่สุดพวกนั้นก็ยอมแพ้จนได้
Suddenly, a duplicate dropped into a waterspout
อยู่ๆ ตัวก๊อปปี้ก็หล่นลงไปในพวยน้ำ
What is going on?
เกิดเรื่องอะไรขึ้นนะ
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Underwater Conspiracy"
"แกะน้อยสุดกวนกับหมาป่าจอมป่วน ตอน ขบวนการก่อการร้ายใต้น้ำ"
I can't become one again if one is missing.
ฉันจะกลับคืนร่างเดิมไม่ได้ถ้าหายไปตัวหนึ่ง
What should we do?
เราจะทำยังไงกันดีล่ะ
Wolffy, let's go down to save that duplicate.
วูฟฟี่ งั้นลงไปช่วยตัวก๊อปปี้กันเถอะ
Sure.
ได้เลย
It's rare to see Wolffy so enthusiastic.
ไม่ค่อยเห็นวูฟฟี่กระตือรือร้นแบบนี้เลยนะ
I don't want to be like this for the rest of my life!
ฉันไม่อยากอยู่ในสภาพนี้ไปตลอดชีวิตนะ!
Come on, let's go down the waterspout in Magic Train.
เร็วเข้า ใช้รถไฟวิเศษขับเข้าไปในพวยน้ำกัน
You're not driving Sirius?
นายไม่ขับซิริอุสลงไปล่ะ
A waterspout is so dangerous.
พวยน้ำอันตรายจะตายไป
What if my precious Sirius gets damaged?
ถ้าซิริอุสล้ำค่าของฉันพังไปล่ะจะทำยังไง
Magic Train...
รถไฟวิเศษๆ...
Weslie, this is the oxygen spray.
เวสลี่ นี่คือสเปรย์ออกซิเจน
Spray it on your body and you can breathe under water.
เอาไว้ฉีดตามตัวจะได้หายใจใต้น้ำได้
It's very chaotic inside a waterspout. Contact us if anything happens.
ในพวยน้ำมันจะวุ่นวายมาก ถ้ามีเรื่องอะไรล่ะก็ติดต่อเราได้เลยนะ
Okay. Let's go!
ได้เลยฮะ ไปกันเลย!
My plan worked!
แผนของฉันได้ผลซะด้วยสิ!
We came to save you!
เรามาช่วยนายแล้ว!
One, two...
หนึ่ง สอง...
three…
สาม...
Come on, give me your hand.
เร็วเข้า ส่งมือมาสิ!
I've finally grouped all my duplicates.
ในที่สุดก็รวมตัวก๊อปปี้ฉันได้ทั้งหมดแล้ว
Now we shall combine!
คราวนี้เราก็มารวมร่างกันเถอะ!
Wonderful! I'm back to normal now.
วิเศษเลย! ฉันกลับคืนร่างเดิมได้แล้ว!
Weslie!
เวสลี่!
Hold on tight!
จับไว้แน่นๆ นะ!
Thank goodness you and the sky crystal are both all right.
โล่งอกไปที นายกับคริสตัลเมฆาปลอดภัยทั้งคู่
Weslie...
เวสลี่...
You don't have to thank me.
ไม่ต้องขอบใจฉันหรอก
No, I want to say--
ไม่ใช่ ฉันอยากจะบอกว่า...
Really, you don't have to thank me.
จริงๆ นะ ไม่ต้องขอบใจฉันหรอก
No, I just wanted to ask, if you're here, who is controlling Magic Train?
ไม่ใช่ ฉันอยากถามว่า ถ้านายอยู่ตรงนี้แล้วใครบังคับรถไฟวิเศษล่ะ
Let's fix Magic Train as soon as we can.
รีบเร่งมือซ่อมรถไฟวิเศษให้เร็วที่สุดกันเถอะ
Luckily, we didn't drive Sirius down here.
โชคดีนะที่เราไม่ได้ขับซิริอุสลงมาที่นี่
Weslie, are you all right?
เวสลี่ เป็นอะไรรึเปล่า
We're fine, but Magic Train is broken.
เราไม่เป็นไรฮะ แต่รถไฟวิเศษพังไปแล้วฮะ
What about the sky crystal?
แล้วคริสตัลเมฆาล่ะ
The sky crystal is with me.
คริสตัลเมฆาอยู่กับผม
The sky crystal doesn't work underwater.
คริสตัลเมฆาใช้ไม่ได้เมื่ออยู่ใต้น้ำ
Hurry back up after you've fixed Magic Train.
ซ่อมรถไฟวิเศษเสร็จแล้วก็รีบกลับมานะ
Stay safe!
ระวังตัวด้วยนะฮะ!
With me, Wolffy, around, he is absolutely safe.
ถ้ามีวูฟฟี่อยู่ด้วยก็ต้องปลอดภัยอยู่แล้วล่ะ
It's not safe because you're around!
จะไม่ปลอดภัยก็เพราะมีคุณอยู่นั่นแหละ!
Is it an earthquake?
แผ่นดินไหวเหรอ
-Magic Train! -Don't worry about it. Run over there!
- รถไฟวิเศษ! - ไม่ต้องห่วงมันหรอก วิ่งไปด้านโน้นเร็ว!
Weslie is in danger! We have to go save him.
เวสลี่ตกอยู่ในอันตราย! เราต้องไปช่วยเขานะ
But we don't have Magic Train. How can we get down there?
แต่เราไม่มีรถไฟวิเศษ เราจะลงไปที่นั่นได้ยังไง
Let's go find Sirius.
งั้นไปตามหาซิริอุสกันเถอะ
Luckily, we ran away quickly.
โชคดีนะที่เราวิ่งหนีกันเร็วอ่ะ
Is anyone here...
มีใครอยู่ที่นี่ไหม...
Is someone trapped by the fallen rocks?
มีใครติดอยู่ในกองหินถล่มนั่นเหรอ
Come on, let's go in and take a look.
เร็วเถอะ เข้าไปดูข้างในกัน
Magic Train is damaged!
รถไฟวิเศษพังหมดแล้ว!
Are Weslie and Wolffy all right?
เวสลี่กับวูฟฟี่ยังโอเคกันอยู่ไหม
Weslie!
เวสลี่!
Weslie, where are you?
เวสลี่ อยู่ไหนน่ะ
Wolffy! Weslie and Wolffy aren't in here.
วูฟฟี่!
Wolffy...
วูฟฟี่...
Mom, has Dad gone missing?
แม่ฮะ พ่อหายตัวไปเหรอฮะ
No. Dad is just playing hide-and-seek with us.
ไม่ใช่จ้ะ พ่อกำลังเล่นซ่อนหากับเราน่ะ
Then I can surely find Dad.
ถ้างั้นผมต้องหาพ่อเจอแน่ๆ เลยฮะ
They should be around here.
พวกเขาน่าจะอยู่แถวๆ นี้แหละ
Then we'll go and find them.
ถ้างั้นเราจะไปตามหาพวกเขา
Chief, please stay here and wait for news.
หัวหน้า อยู่ที่นี่แล้วรอฟังข่าวนะ
Okay, I'll stay behind to fix Magic Train just in case.
ได้เลย ฉันจะอยู่ซ่อมรถไฟวิเศษเผื่อไว้ละกัน
We'll go and find them too.
เราก็จะไปตามหาพวกเขา
It's too dangerous underwater. You two should stay here.
ใต้น้ำนั่นอันตรายเกินไป ทั้งคู่อยู่ที่นี่แหละ
Yes. We can't afford to lose Willie while we're trying to find Wolffy.
ใช่ค่ะ เราคงไม่อยากเสียวิลลี่ไป ในขณะที่พยายามตามหาวูฟฟี่นะคะ
All right.
ก็ได้
They're not here.
พวกเขาไม่ได้อยู่ที่นี่นะ
They're not here either.
พวกเขาไม่อยู่ที่นี่เหมือนกัน
I've searched over there, but can't find them either.
ฉันค้นทางโน้นแล้วแต่ไม่เจอพวกเขาเลย
Weslie!
เวสลี่!
I'm here!
ฉันอยู่ตรงนี้!
It's Weslie's voice!
นั่นเสียงเวสลี่นี่นา!
It seems to have come from the cave.
ฟังดูเหมือนมาจากในถ้ำนะฮะ
Weslie!
เวสลี่!
I'm here!
ฉันอยู่ตรงนี้!
Weslie's here!
เวสลี่อยู่ที่นี่จริงๆ ด้วย!
You came!
พวกนายมาแล้ว!
Why are you trapped?
ทำไมนายติดอยู่ในกับดักล่ะ
We'll save you!
เราจะช่วยนายเอง!
Weslie, are you all right?
เวสลี่ เป็นอะไรรึเปล่า
I'm fine.
ฉันไม่เป็นไรหรอก
There are traps here. Be careful, everyone.
มีกับดักอยู่ในนี้นะ ทุกคนระวังตัวกันด้วยล่ะ
Then let's get out of here immediately.
ถ้างั้นรีบออกไปจากที่นี่กันดีกว่า
Stay close and don't lose anyone.
เกาะกลุ่มกันไว้อย่าให้ใครหลุดไปล่ะ
Can't you see such a handsome wolf here?
นี่ไม่เห็นหมาป่ารูปหล่ออยู่ตรงนี้รึไงเนี่ย
I forgot Wolffy is here too.
ฉันลืมไปเลยว่าวูฟฟี่ก็อยู่ที่นี่ด้วย
You're not that bad after all.
จะว่าไปนายก็ใช้ได้เหมือนกันนะ
Wolnie and Willie came too. Let's get out of here quickly.
โวลนี่กับวิลลี่ก็มาด้วย รีบออกไปจากที่นี่กันเถอะ
Willie, Dad's coming!
วิลลี่ พ่อมาแล้ว!
Wolffy, you're running too fast.
วูฟฟี่ วิ่งเร็วเกินไปแล้วนะ
Can't you see such a cute fish here?
นี่นายไม่เห็นปลาน่ารักติดอยู่ตรงนี้เลยเหรอ
Oh, right, there's a little fish too.
เออจริงสิ มีปลาน้อยอยู่ที่นี่ด้วย
Right, why were you trapped here?
ว่าแต่ทำไมคุณถึงมาติดกับดักอยู่ที่นี่ล่ะ
Weslie and I heard a voice, so we went into the cave.
เวสลี่กับฉันได้ยินเสียง เราก็เลยเข้าไปในถ้ำน่ะสิ
We found this little fish trapped inside.
เราเจอปลาน้อยติดกับดักอยู่ข้างใน
I went to save him because I'm kind and ended up trapped with Weslie.
ฉันอยากช่วยปลาน้อยเพราะฉันใจดี แต่กลายเป็นว่าต้องมาติดกับดักพร้อมเวสลี่
I went into the cave to hide from the falling rocks,
ผมเข้าถ้ำมาเพื่อจะหลบหินถล่ม
then a dark shadow passed behind me,
จากนั้นก็มีเงามืดเคลื่อนที่ผ่านด้านหลังไป
and I was caught in a trap.
แล้วผมก็ติดอยู่ในกับดักนี่แหละ
A dark shadow?
เงามืดเหรอ
I'm finally done fixing Magic Train.
ในที่สุดฉันก็ซ่อมรถไฟวิเศษเสร็จซะที
Mommy, I see Dad.
แม่ฮะ ผมเจอพ่อแล้วฮะ
This must be the data recorder of Magic Train.
นี่คงเป็นเทปบันทึกภาพของรถไฟวิเศษ
Hold on.
เดี๋ยวก่อนนะ
Did he cause the rocks to fall?
เขาคือต้นเหตุที่ทำให้หินถล่มเหรอเนี่ย
Village Chief.
หัวหน้าหมู่บ้าน
Children, glad to know you're all right.
เด็กๆ ดีใจจังเลยที่ได้รู้ว่าไม่เป็นไรกันนะ
Weslie, you have to be careful!
เวสลี่ นายต้องระวังนะ!
That fish might be a villain.
เจ้าปลานั่นอาจจะเป็นจอมวายร้ายก็ได้นะ
Weslie...
เวสลี่...
Weslie! Little fish, what are you doing?
เวสลี่!
Little fish?
เจ้าปลาน้อยเหรอ
Who told you I'm a fish?
ใครบอกเธอว่าฉันเป็นปลาล่ะ
Oh, no, I'm stuck... Give me a little time.
ไม่นะ มันติดอ่ะ ขอเวลาฉันแป๊ปนึงนะ
This is...
นี่มัน...
A black cloud person?
ชาวเมฆาทมิฬนี่นา
I've been lying low among you for a long time.
ฉันแอบซ่อนตัวอยู่กับพวกนายมาตั้งนาน
The video camera on Magic Train,
กล้องวิดีโอบนรถไฟวิเศษ
the note picked up by Mechanical Bird, I did all that.
กระดาษโน้ตที่หุ่นยนต์นกเก็บได้ ฝีมือฉันทั้งนั้นแหละ
In order to get the sky crystal,
เพื่อให้ได้คริสตัลเมฆา
I even lured you to go underwater.
ฉันหลอกล่อนายให้ลงไปใต้น้ำ
But I didn't expect you to escape from the falling rocks.
แต่ไม่คิดว่านายจะหนีจากหินถล่มได้นะ
I see. You pretended to be trapped and lured us into the cave.
เข้าใจแล้ว นายแกล้งติดกับดัก แล้วหลอกให้เราเข้าถ้ำไป
No. Actually, I wanted to lure you into the cave.
ไม่ใช่ จริงๆ แล้วฉันอยากหลอกล่อให้นายเข้าถ้ำ
When you came close to me, I would press the red button and trap you.
พอนายเข้าใกล้ฉัน ฉันจะกดปุ่มแดงนี่เพื่อให้นายติดกับดัก
But there's dirt on such a perfect remote control!
แต่มีสิ่งสกปรกติดอยู่ที่รีโมต!
I can't let that happen.
ฉันจะปล่อยให้เป็นแบบนี้ไม่ได้
I pressed the wrong button!
ฉันกดปุ่มผิด!
So I modified my plan and continued to lure you.
ฉันจึงปรับแผนใหม่และหลอกล่อนายต่อไป
I'm here!
ฉันอยู่ตรงนี้!
Someone's trapped. We'll save you.
มีใครก็ไม่รู้ติดกับดักอยู่ เรามาช่วยแล้ว!
I intended to trap you after you saved me.
ฉันตั้งใจจะจับนายหลังจากที่ช่วยฉันแล้ว
However, I left a thread on the remote control when I wiped it.
แต่ตอนเช็ดรีโมตดันมีด้ายติดมาด้วย
We're trapped too.
- เราก็ติดกับดักเหมือนกันเลย - ด้วยเหตุนี้แหละเราถึงติดกับดักกันหมดไงล่ะ
It doesn't matter anymore because I've got the sky crystal!
แต่ไม่เป็นไรแล้วล่ะ เพราะฉันมีคริสตัลเมฆา!
-What do you need the sky crystal for? -I'm going to destroy it.
- นายจะเอาคริสตัลเมฆาไปทำไม - ฉันจะทำลายมันน่ะสิ!
That is my gem. I won't let you destroy it.
นั่นมันเพชรของฉัน ฉันไม่ยอมให้นายทำลายมันหรอก
Give it back to me.
เอาคืนมานะ
Let's help Wolffy.
ไปช่วยวูฟฟี่กันเถอะ
I caught him.
ฉันจับเขาได้แล้ว
Really?
จริงเหรอ
You can't escape. Give in now.
นายหนีไม่รอดแน่ ยอมแพ้ซะเถอะ
I won't give in easily.
ฉันไม่ยอมแพ้ง่ายๆ หรอก
Goodbye, everyone!
ลาก่อนนะทุกคน!
Don't go!
อย่าเพิ่งไปสิ!
Children...
พวกเด็กๆ...
Are you all right?
เป็นอะไรกันรึเปล่า
Village Chief, the sky crystal was taken. Let's hurry and get it back.
หัวหน้าหมู่บ้าน เจ้านั่นเอาคริสตัลเมฆาไปแล้ว รีบตามไปเอากลับคืนมาเถอะ
Wolnie, Willie, this place is too dangerous. Let's get out of here.
โวลนี่ วิลลี่ ที่นี่อันตรายเกินไป เรารีบไปจากที่นี่กันเถอะ
Wolffy, aren't you going to help us chase the villain?
วูฟฟี่ จะช่วยตามล่าเจ้าวายร้ายนั่นไม่ใช่เหรอ
I don't get myself involved in dangerous things like that.
ฉันไม่เอาตัวไปยุ่งเรื่องอันตรายแบบนั้นหรอก
I'm taking my wife and son away from this dangerous place.
ฉันจะพาลูกและเมียไปจากที่ที่อันตรายแบบนี้ซะ
In that case, we'll chase the villain ourselves.
ถ้างั้นเราก็ต้องตามล่าเจ้าวายร้ายนั่นเองแล้วล่ะ
Okay.
ได้เลย
TO BE CONTINUED
(โปรดติดตามตอนต่อไป)